Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Digital Collections and Archives Records
2001 -- 2012
1662 -- 2016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Digital Collections and Archives
UA069
15.55 Linear Feet 15 boxes and 1 oversize folder.
561 Digital Object(s) Of the 581 digital objects in the collection, 1 represents a zip file of CIDER comprising 40.7 MB of data.
This collection contains the records of the Tufts University Digital Collections and Archives, including administrative records, collection documentation, grant documents, exhibit materials, and publications.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by DCA, 2008-2018. 2018 accession: UA-2018-061.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Collection documentation; Administrative files; Publications; Grants and project records; Digital objects; and Exhibit related materials.
Biographical / Historical
Digital Collections and Archives is the Tufts University steward for all archival records and materials of significant and historical relevance to the college.
The collection began as the University Archives, which were incorporated in 1965 by the Tufts University Board of Trustees (Annual Reports 1965-1988). Previously, the position of archivist was loosely created in 1959 as a means of processing and acquiring important university and student records for preservation. This role was filled by Tufts history professor and historian Russell L. Miller, who also wrote the Tufts University history "Light on the Hill." The archives were considered a department of the University Library (known as Eaton and then Wessell at that time), overseen by the College of Arts, Sciences and Engineering.
The university's archives were first kept in Eaton Library, but moved to the Wessell Library building in 1965. Originals of some records were sent to vaults in Ballou Hall for storage. In 1991, due to budget issues, the university archivist was laid off. When the office was reopened in 1997, it was as the University Archives and Special Collections, also located as a department within the Tisch Library.
In July 2001, Digital Collections and Archives was created when the University Archives was tasked with developing a Tufts Digital Library. The department moved from the College of Arts, Science and Engineering to the Central Administration, directed by the University Provost. The Special Collections department remained under Tisch Library.
DCA is currently physically housed in Tisch Library building.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the office records of the Digital Collections and Archives. The records document the administration and activities of the department and its projects, including the "Fedora and the Preservation of University Records" project and the Tufts Accessioning Program for Electronic Records (TAPER). Included are annual reports, accession logs, description and policy documents, correspondence, publication material by and about DCA, administrative planning documents, and material relating to grants and grant-funded projects. The majority of digital objects in this collection are materials digitized by DCA. The bulk of the material dates from 2001-2012.
Exhibitions; Digital Collections and Archives; Archival materials--Digitization.; Academic Support -- Libraries, Galleries, Archives
- Collection documentation, 2001 -- 2016; UA069.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object containing 1 zip file.; 40.7 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains files documenting collections, as well as a zip file of CIDER, DCA's former collection management system.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  - 2001 - 2005 DCA copyright / permission form request, UA069.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Open for research.
  - 2006 DCA copyright / permission form request, UA069.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - 2007 - 2008 DCA copyright / permission form request, UA069.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - CIDER, 2016-08-19; UA069.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object containing 1 zip file.; 40.7 Megabytes
    75 years from the date of creation.
    This item is a zip file of CIDER, DCA's former collection management system. Data entry in CIDER was frozen as of August 17, 2016; as of September 2, 2016, ArchivesSpace became the content management system of record for DCA.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Accessioned in 2018, accession UA-2018-061.
- Administrative files, 1877 -- 2014; 1997 -- 2013; UA069.002; 2.3 Linear Feet
  This series contains general office files, including those of the Records Archivist, University Records Manager, and Director and University Archivist. Other material includes general administrative documents and policies and procedures. Material in this series ranges from 1877-2014, with the majority of material dating from 1997-2013.
  - Records Archivist files, 1985 -- 2012; 1997 -- 2012; UA069.002.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
    This series contains materials compiled by the former Records Archivist, Veronica Martzahl, from 2007-2013. The Records Archivist has primary responsibility for accessioning archival materials and establishing intellectual and physical control over them, and a large part of this series consists of accession logs. It also includes meeting materials, website design records, and administrative planning documents. Materials date from 1985-2012, with the majority of the materials dating from 1997-2012.
    - Policies and procedures wiki training materials, 2008 September 24; UA069.002.001.008.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1)
      20 years from date of creation.
    - RM training for Tisch materials, 2012 April - May; UA069.002.001.008.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Website revamp materials, 2007 -- 2008; UA069.002.001.008.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - PREMIS party meeting materials, 2009 -- 2010; UA069.002.001.008.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Jackson web exhibit materials, 2006 -- 2010; UA069.002.001.008.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Data management working papers, 2007 November; UA069.002.001.008.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Benchmark notes, circa 2000s; UA069.002.001.008.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Action planning committee papers, 2011 August - October; UA069.002.001.008.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - APC materials, 2010 -- 2011; UA069.002.001.008.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Strategic planning materials, 2003 -- 2009; UA069.002.001.008.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Retrievex records, 2008 -- 2012; UA069.002.001.008.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - DCAPE materials, 2010 April - September; UA069.002.001.008.00013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
    - Accession logs, circa 1985 -- 1996; UA069.002.001.008.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Pre-1997 accession records, 1989 -- 1996; UA069.002.001.008.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - FY1998 accession records, 1997 -- 1998; UA069.002.001.008.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - FY1999 accession records, 1998 -- 1999; UA069.002.001.008.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - FY2000 accession records, 1999 -- 2000; UA069.002.001.008.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - FY2001 accession records, 2000 -- 2001; UA069.002.001.008.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - FY2002 accession records, 2001 -- 2002; UA069.002.001.008.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - FY2003 accession records, 2002 -- 2003; UA069.002.001.008.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - FY2004 accession records, 2003 -- 2004; UA069.002.001.008.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - FY2005 accession records, 2004 -- 2005; UA069.002.001.008.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - FY2006 accession records, 2005 -- 2006; UA069.002.001.008.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - FY2007 accession records, 2006 -- 2007; UA069.002.001.008.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - FY2008 accession log, 2007 -- 2008; UA069.002.001.008.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - FY2009 accession log, 2008 -- 2009; UA069.002.001.008.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - FY2010 accession log, 2009 -- 2010; UA069.002.001.008.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - FY2011 accession log, 2010 -- 2011; UA069.002.001.008.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - University Records Manager files, 1989 -- 2013; 1998 -- 2013; UA069.002.002; 0.8 Linear Feet
    This series contains materials compiled by the former University Records Manager, Eliot Wilczek, from 2002-2013. The University Records Manager helps university offices efficiently manage their records, and this series includes information on the Tufts Records Management Program as well as administrative reports, correspondence, meeting materials, and policy and procedures documents. Materials date from 1989-2013, with the majority of the materials dating from 1998-2013.
    - Records schedules, circa 1998 -- 2000; UA069.002.002.009.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Records management procedure manual, circa 2001; UA069.002.002.009.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Internal audit newsletters, 2002 -- 2003; UA069.002.002.009.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Retrievex correspondence, 2013 December 24; UA069.002.002.009.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - ARMS correspondence, 2004 March - May; UA069.002.002.009.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Retrievex email, 2008 May 30; UA069.002.002.009.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - ARMS to Retrievex announcement letter, 2007 October 25; UA069.002.002.009.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - ARMS prices letter, 2007 March 1; UA069.002.002.009.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - ARMS agreement and prices, 2000 -- 2004; UA069.002.002.009.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - ARMS reports, 2001 -- 2002; UA069.002.002.009.00010; 2 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
    - Policies and procedures meeting materials, 2006 May - July; UA069.002.002.009.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - FEDORA materials, 2003 February - April; UA069.002.002.009.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Digital space planning summary, circa 2004; UA069.002.002.009.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - FEDORA timeline and meetings materials, 2004 January - May; UA069.002.002.009.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Digital Library search materials, 2005 November - December; UA069.002.002.009.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - TDR Public Explanation, 2005 August 29; UA069.002.002.009.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - TDR policies materials, circa 2004; UA069.002.002.009.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - T-NEMC Archives report materials, 1989, 2005 -- 2006; UA069.002.002.009.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Records retention policy materials, 2006 -- 2007; UA069.002.002.009.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Records authority statement materials, circa 2006; UA069.002.002.009.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Patriot Act policy materials, 2003 April - December; UA069.002.002.009.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "Library policies revised to address Patriot Act" Tufts Daily article, 2003 October 2; UA069.002.002.009.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Patriot Act policies and memos, 2003 February - April; UA069.002.002.009.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Creator records, 2006 January - February; UA069.002.002.009.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - FY03 annual report, 2002 -- 2003; UA069.002.002.009.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Vertical file weeding project summary, 2004 January; UA069.002.002.009.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - DCA structure proposal, circa 2004; UA069.002.002.009.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Annual planning materials, 2002 -- 2003; UA069.002.002.009.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - RM procedures materials, 2002 July; UA069.002.002.009.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Retention policy and schedule materials, 2004 December; UA069.002.002.009.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Financial records and retention schedules, 2004 November 22; UA069.002.002.009.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Space planning materials, 2004 January 5; UA069.002.002.009.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Strategic planning final draft, 2003 April 17; UA069.002.002.009.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Strategic planning drafts and segments, circa 2003; UA069.002.002.009.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Strategic planning process materials, 2002 September; UA069.002.002.009.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Internal analysis materials, 2003 January; UA069.002.002.009.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - External analysis materials, 2002 December; UA069.002.002.009.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Benchmarking materials, 2003 January; UA069.002.002.009.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - FEDORA DCA-AT meeting materials, 2003 -- 2005; UA069.002.002.009.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Brochure and bookmarks, circa 2002; UA069.002.002.009.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Tufts photo collaborative meeting notes, 2004 August 18; UA069.002.002.009.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Tufts Records Management Program materials, 2000, 2002; UA069.002.002.009.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - RM brochure, circa 2000; UA069.002.002.009.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Managing University Records packet, 1998 March 19; UA069.002.002.009.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Policy website discussion summary, 2011 March 11; UA069.002.002.009.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Howard University presentation materials, 2007 February 22; UA069.002.002.009.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Harvard RM 3/8 visit materials, circa 2006 January; UA069.002.002.009.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - E-Discovery meeting materials, 2007 June 26; UA069.002.002.009.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - E-Discovery 2/1 meeting materials, 2008 January - February; UA069.002.002.009.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - E-Discovery Deke interview materials, 2008 July 9; UA069.002.002.009.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - E-Discovery 9/9 meeting materials, 2008 August - September; UA069.002.002.009.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - E-Discovery 10/16 meeting materials, 2008 October 17; UA069.002.002.009.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - E-Discovery assessment, circa 2008; UA069.002.002.009.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - E-Discovery workflow, 2008 -- 2009; UA069.002.002.009.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Data destruction materials, circa 2008; UA069.002.002.009.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Data destruction proposal draft, 2008 May 15; UA069.002.002.009.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Information destruction materials, 2007 -- 2013; UA069.002.002.009.00057; 2 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 58-59)
    - Accessioning procedures materials, 2005 December; UA069.002.002.009.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Internal audit email policy report, 2002 March 11; UA069.002.002.009.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Internal audit records management materials, 1998 -- 2000; UA069.002.002.009.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Meeting maker upgrade materials, 2005, 2008; UA069.002.002.009.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Brandeis visit materials, 2006 July; UA069.002.002.009.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Yale ERA report, circa 2003; UA069.002.002.009.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Recordkeeping system comparison materials, 2007 -- 2008; UA069.002.002.009.00064; 3 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 66-68)
    - Retention schedules materials, 2004 -- 2010; UA069.002.002.009.00065; 2 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
    - DCA pilot implementation materials, 2008 September; UA069.002.002.009.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Emergency plan materials, 2005 November 15; UA069.002.002.009.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - TCCS security policy materials, 2003 -- 2004; UA069.002.002.009.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - University security policy materials, 2001 -- 2002; UA069.002.002.009.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Records advisory group materials, 2004 -- 2006; UA069.002.002.009.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Retention policies materials, 1998 -- 2002; UA069.002.002.009.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - DCA ID management materials, 2004 November - December; UA069.002.002.009.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Grant narrative records, circa 2003 -- 2008; UA069.002.002.009.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - NHPRC lobby materials, 2005 -- 2008; UA069.002.002.009.00074; 3 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 79-81)
    - ASE faculty presentation materials, 2005 -- 2006; UA069.002.002.009.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Sackler School presentation materials, 2005 -- 2006; UA069.002.002.009.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - University records policies and DCA factsheet, circa 2007; UA069.002.002.009.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Policies and procedures, 1956 -- 2008; 1999 -- 2008; UA069.002.003; 0.3 Linear Feet
    This series contains material relating to policies and procedures at DCA. Much of the material is composed of disaster plans. Other records include policies and procedures for the front desk, accessioning, and reference services. The material dates from 1956-2008, with the bulk created between 1999-2008.
    - Archives and special collections descriptions and policies, circa 1989; UA069.002.003.010.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Old or original archives policy materials, 1956 -- 1995; UA069.002.003.010.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Plan FY2004-2008, 2003 April 17; UA069.002.003.010.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - DCA policies and procedures material, 2000 -- 2005; UA069.002.003.010.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Tisch disaster plan, 1999 -- 2001; UA069.002.003.010.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Disaster plan materials, 1999 May 26; UA069.002.003.010.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - DCA disaster plan, 2001 June 26; UA069.002.003.010.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - DCA disaster plan, 2006; UA069.002.003.010.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - DCA partial D-plan, 2007; UA069.002.003.010.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - DCA reference procedures binder, circa 2003 -- 2008; UA069.002.003.010.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Tufts procedures manual binder, 2000 -- 2002; UA069.002.003.010.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - DCA front desk and administrative procedures binder, 2005 -- 2008; UA069.002.003.010.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Wiki policy and procedure presentation, 2008 September 29; UA069.002.003.010.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Accessioning procedures materials, circa 2005 December 7; UA069.002.003.010.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - General administrative files, 1877 -- 2014; 2001 -- 2004; UA069.002.004; 0.5 Linear Feet
    This series contains a variety of administrative records, including reports, statistics, correspondence, and committee materials (specifically from the University Gifts of Art Committee). Much of the material concerns the annual University Committee on Teaching and Faculty Development (UCTFD). Material dates from 1877 -2014, with the majority of the materials dating from 2001-2004.
    - Archives and special collections general materials and gifts, 1877 -- 1995; UA069.002.004.010.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - University Records Manager annual report FY2002, 2003; UA069.002.004.010.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Annual reports, 1962 -- 1988; UA069.002.004.010.00017; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Pre-1997 archives committee correspondence, 1961 -- 1986; UA069.002.004.010.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Annual report FY 2006, circa 2006; UA069.002.004.010.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Tufts UCTFD materials, 2003 -- 2008; UA069.002.004.010.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - FY2009 and FY2010 UCTFD materials, 2007 -- 2010; UA069.002.004.010.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - FY2011 UCTFD materials, 2010 -- 2011; UA069.002.004.010.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - FY2012 UCTFD materials, 2009 -- 2012; UA069.002.004.010.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - FY2013 UCTFD materials, 2012 -- 2013; UA069.002.004.010.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - FY2014 UCTFD materials, 2013 -- 2014; UA069.002.004.010.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - University Gifts of Art Committee materials, 2006 -- 2007; UA069.002.004.010.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Reference statistics binder, 2001 -- 2003; UA069.002.004.010.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Special Collections retrieval records, 2001 -- 2005; UA069.002.004.010.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Reference log and other projects notebook, 2012 -- 2013; UA069.002.004.010.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Director's files, 2005 -- 2009; UA069.002.005; 0.2 Linear Feet
    This series contains materials compiled by the former Director and University Archivist, Anne Sauer, from 2004-2014. The Director and University Archivist oversees the Digital Collections and Archives staff, collections, and operations. The series includes correspondence, chiefly about a proposed acquisition regarding the history of radio at Tufts. Material dates from 2005-2009.
    - Correspondence, UA069.002.005.010.046 (Box 10, Folder 46-54)
    - Anne Sauer's office files and untitled cds, circa 1998 -- 2003; UA069.002.005.010.00055 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Publications, 2001 -- 2010; UA069.003; 0.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials published by or about DCA. It includes promotional material, conference material, bookmarks, brochures, prints, photographs, and Tufts University by Anne Sauer, an overview of the history of the university. This series includes digital media. The bulk of the materials date from 2001-2010.
  - Digital Collections and Archives brochures, circa 2001; UA069.003.010.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "What is a Digital Library" by Pauline Stieff, 2005 March; UA069.003.010.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - John Holmes poetry walk materials, circa 2003 April 11; UA069.003.010.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - DCA bookmarks, circa 2002; UA069.003.010.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - DCA brochures, circa 2004; UA069.003.010.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Edward R. Murrow Papers promotional material, circa 2008; UA069.003.010.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Photos of DCA and MacJannet collection processing, circa 2002; UA069.003.010.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - DCA photographs, circa 2004; UA069.003.010.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - "Ballou Hall and Goddard Chapel" by George Guzzi, circa 1995; UA069.003.010.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - DCA blog promotional cards, 2009 September; UA069.003.010.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Bookmark materials, circa 2002 -- 2006; UA069.003.010.00039; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 40-41)